Hello friends, how are you all? It will be better.
Minimum is 18 years and maximum is 65 years for
dependent children.
Children from 91 days to 25 years can be
covered in this
and the maximum coverage in this which is famous is
1 year, 2 years, 3 years, which can be taken. So
friends, let's see the benefits. First of all, there is
no capping in this for room rent. If you can take submersible, you get a discount in it. 7.30 percent for two years and 10% for three years. You get a maximum discount of ₹10,000. You can do that. If you want to make a statement, there is no capping in it. Now you can
take Ayurvedic, Unani, Siddha, Homeopathy in-patient treatment.
You can cover the treatment of both the organs.
Restore
benefit is 100%. You can take restore benefit.
It has
worldwide coverage. In this policy, it has
worldwide coverage but there is a
small condition in it. Your policy  The minimum amount should be Rs.
2500000 or above only then
these benefits will be available to you
Home credit
submission Maximum Rs. 25000 Health checkup
can be taken annually starting from Rs.
Animal fight vaccination is
also covered in it but
50% of the problem and maximum Rs. 10 lakh There
is a small condition in this also that the policy should be at
least Rs. 10 lakh or above
and its waiting period is of 3 years
Apart from this there are such value added services like
unlimited 24*7 video or
telemedicine online chat with the doctor,
this feature is also inbuilt in it, you
can take the benefit of this also
Friends optional benefit Some
optional benefit is being given in this for which you will have to pay
some extra premium, then
you can take the benefit now like first
maternity benefit, it gives you coverage up to Rs. 10 lakh and
10% of maximum Rs. 10 lakh and there is a
condition in this when you pay the policy together in 3 years  Only then you
can avail this benefit,
you cannot avail such writer's honor vice and its waiting
period is only 9 months,
new baby cover,
whatever the matric cover, will be
available for vaccination, I would
like to tell you that in case of personal accident, it will keep
increasing, this is not a year,
if you are taking this policy, then the non-
paper items in it become part of the table items, so
friends, now let us talk about the
waiting period, the
initial waiting period in this is 30
days,
accident is covered from the first day,
if there is any, then it is covered after 2 years, its
specific waiting period is 2
years, the specifications are
like character or stone or
hernia, such diseases are covered for two years,
as we talked about earlier, this is covered for 3 years, if
not then
friends, I hope you
liked this video, if you have
any questions, you can comment in the comment box, so
friends, we will meet
in the next video, thank you